skymilesshopping.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Shop Online at SkyMiles Shopping

The Delta Skymiles Shopping Mall has the highest respect for our Members' privacy and personal information. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, the Delta SkyMiles Shopping Mall (the "Program") will never release a Member's personal information without express permission except for purposes of data verification and supplementation or such uses as are described in the Terms and Conditions.

Cartera Commerce, Inc., a Delaware corporation ("Cartera Commerce"), is the provider of the Program, which is sponsored by Delta Air Lines, Inc. and/or its affiliates (collectively, the "Program Sponsor"). This Privacy Policy describes Cartera's handling of your personal information it may collect through your participation in the Program.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT

In order to participate in the Program, you are required to provide certain required information, including without limitation your name, address, e-mail address, and phone number.

We automatically log your IP address when you visit the Program website. The information logged allows us to track a user throughout their visit to the Program website. We do not use this information to capture demographic or other information; rather, it is used simply in the administration of the Program website.

The nature of the Program requires us to obtain information about your purchases at participating merchants. As a result, participating merchants send us transaction information (date and time of transaction, temporary ID number which only the Program can link to your account, sale amount and returned goods information) on a frequent basis. Cartera Commerce and/or the Program Sponsor use this information to properly add the miles you've earned to your Delta SkyMiles® Program account (the "Program Account").

Information that identifies you personally will not be provided to, sold or disclosed to any third party without your express permission. Within Cartera Commerce and/or the Program Sponsor, we restrict access to your data to those employees, such as customer service representatives, who need such access to better serve you. In addition, Cartera Commerce and/or the Program Sponsor provide limited access to third party vendors who provide financial, administrative or other services in support of the Program. These vendors are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services to the Program and may not otherwise use or resell the data.

You will not be able to log on to the Program website without enabling your browser to accept cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our Web server directly or using an authorized third party. The Program uses cookies when you log on to your account with your User Name and Password. These cookies allow us to remember you as you visit pages in the Program site, so that you do not need to reenter your information. Our usage of cookies also allows us to track where users go when they visit the Program site, including crediting you with Miles to your Account for each Qualifying Transaction. We may use this "click-stream data" to deliver targeted offers or messaging to Members and other similar functionality. We also may use these cookies to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information to customize your experience and enable us to continually improve the quality of the Program.

The Program site contains a number of links to merchants' web sites. We have not undertaken a review of the privacy policies or terms and conditions at such merchants' web sites, and we make no representations about the privacy policies or levels of security at these sites or the applicable terms and conditions. We are not responsible for the applicable terms and conditions or the privacy practices used by such merchants.

We will be sending you e-mails on a regular basis to advise you when your account statement has been updated. Other e-mails may be sent from the Program informing you of updates or changes to the network, etc.

The Program site takes commercially reasonable precautions consistent with general industry practices to protect Members' information. When Members submit sensitive information via the Program site, we use our commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that their information is protected both online and off-line.

Information provided during our join or edit profile pages is encrypted and is protected with what is generally recognized as the best available encryption software in the industry - SSL. You will see the lock icon at the bottom of your browser and if you right click on the page, and view the page properties, you will see the site certificate. To learn more about SSL, follow this link: [http://www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/).

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also use our commercially reasonable efforts consistent with general industry practices to protect user-information off-line. Access to Members' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only individuals who have a need to know such information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all such individuals are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. When an employee is hired, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, off site. If you have any questions about the security at the Program site, users can send an e-mail to [usersupport@cartera.com](mailto:usersupport@cartera.com) or otherwise contact us at the information below./p>

We also will send you Program and service announcement updates. Users are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the Program and associated services. We communicate with Members to provide requested services and address issues relating to their account, via email or phone, with information provided by the Member. It is your responsibility to keep such information current.

You can update your information by going to the "My Profile" link. Your profile changes will take effect immediately. If there is incorrect information in your Statement, please Contact Us and our customer service team will be glad to assist you.

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Program site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information or other information disclosed by you in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an email prior to effecting such change. Members will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. Otherwise, we will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

Though we make commercially reasonable efforts to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on or otherwise in connection with the Program site.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

  * Phone:
  * (781) 541-6800
  * Fax:
  * (781) 541-6801
  * Email:
  *     * Address:
    * Delta Skymiles Shopping Mall  
c/o Cartera Commerce, Inc.  
One Cranberry Hill, Suite 203  
Lexington, MA 02421  
Attn: Customer Care
  * Last Updated:
  * January 28, 2015
